### **Grant Patterson**

227 Vintage Lane Campbellsville, Ky 42718 270-283-2014 <u>darkrider231@gmail.com</u> darkrider231.github.io

https://www.linkedin.com/in/grant-patterson-5b3348207/

## Objective

Seeking employment in a computer related job. Main job I hope to get is web development.

## Summary

Team Assembly/Production Experience

**Team Oriented** 

Machine Operator/Equipment Operator/Quality Control Inspection

Good filling and organizational skills

Experience in handling confidential paperwork

Ability to use Microsoft Office programs

Able to make Windows programs (Windows 8.1+)

Sutdied C# and VB.net, and have some knowledge of android

programming

# **Experience**

## Lawn and Garden, Walmart, Campbellsville, Ky

2015-2015

Cashier, carry outs, watering plants, cleaning up the patio, CVPing plants, stocking, zoning, and returns. Also I had to do seasonal department: Easter, Back-to-School, Halloween, and Christmas. Those I did stocking, zoning, and returns.

#### Overnight Stocker, Walmart, Bowling Green, Ky

2010-2011

Stock up merchandise, clean displays, remove damaged items, and organize displays. Also responsible for adjusting prices as necessary, completing logs and other documentation so that the store know when more products are needed. Identify safety hazards and report apparent theft.

Crisplant/Outbound Departments, Amazon.com, Campbellsville, Ky 2007-2010

Check items for damages, scan bar codes, and put them in a box on a conveyor. Also gathered totes in the department. Made boxes from a box machine. Also did picking as well. Picked certain items from what the scanner tells me where its at, put them in a tote, and put them on a conveyor.

## Cashier/Drive Thru, Dairy Queen, Greensburg, Ky

2003-2005

Take orders from customers in drive thru and front line. Give customers their orders. Also washed dishes, take out the garbage outside, did some yard work as well. During closing times, I took out garbage, cleaned the rails where the seats are at, mopped the floor, and cleaned the bathrooms.

## Education

# **C.I.T. Associate Degree: Programming Track**

Elizabethtown Community and Technical College

June 4<sup>th</sup>, 2014

Also got my I.T. Fundamentals Certificate, and A+ Certification Certificate.

## **BC Skills**

January 18th 2021 - May 7th, 2021

Currently taking a course in BC Skills. I have learned how to build websites in this class. I learned, HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap, Sass, Terminal (VS Code)Git, and JavaScript.